{
  "flashcards" : [ {
    "question" : "あ",
    "answer" : "a",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "い",
    "answer" : "i",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "う",
    "answer" : "u",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "え",
    "answer" : "e",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "お",
    "answer" : "o",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "か",
    "answer" : "ka",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "き",
    "answer" : "ki",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "く",
    "answer" : "ku",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "け",
    "answer" : "ke",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "こ",
    "answer" : "ko",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "さ",
    "answer" : "sa",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "し",
    "answer" : "shi",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "す",
    "answer" : "su",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "せ",
    "answer" : "se",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "そ",
    "answer" : "so",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "た",
    "answer" : "ta",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ち",
    "answer" : "chi",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "つ",
    "answer" : "tsu",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "て",
    "answer" : "te",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "と",
    "answer" : "to",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "な",
    "answer" : "na",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "に",
    "answer" : "ni",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぬ",
    "answer" : "nu",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ね",
    "answer" : "ne",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "の",
    "answer" : "no",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "は",
    "answer" : "ha",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ひ",
    "answer" : "hi",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ふ",
    "answer" : "fu",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "へ",
    "answer" : "he",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ほ",
    "answer" : "ho",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ま",
    "answer" : "ma",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "み",
    "answer" : "mi",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "む",
    "answer" : "mu",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "め",
    "answer" : "me",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "も",
    "answer" : "mo",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "や",
    "answer" : "ya",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ゆ",
    "answer" : "yu",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "よ",
    "answer" : "yo",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ら",
    "answer" : "ra",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "り",
    "answer" : "ri",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "る",
    "answer" : "ru",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "れ",
    "answer" : "re",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ろ",
    "answer" : "ro",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  },{
    "question" : "わ",
    "answer" : "wa",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "を",
    "answer" : "wo",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "ん",
    "answer" : "n",
    "tagged" : ["hiragana", "gojuon"]
  }, {
    "question" : "が",
    "answer" : "ga",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぎ",
    "answer" : "gi",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぐ",
    "answer" : "gu",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "げ",
    "answer" : "ge",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ご",
    "answer" : "go",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ざ",
    "answer" : "za",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "じ",
    "answer" : "ji",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ず",
    "answer" : "zu",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぜ",
    "answer" : "ze",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぞ",
    "answer" : "zo",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "だ",
    "answer" : "da",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぢ",
    "answer" : "di",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "づ",
    "answer" : "du",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "で",
    "answer" : "de",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ど",
    "answer" : "do",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ば",
    "answer" : "ba",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "び",
    "answer" : "bi",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぶ",
    "answer" : "bu",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "べ",
    "answer" : "be",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぼ",
    "answer" : "bo",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぱ",
    "answer" : "pa",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぴ",
    "answer" : "pi",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぷ",
    "answer" : "pu",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぺ",
    "answer" : "pe",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ぽ",
    "answer" : "po",
    "tagged" : [ "hiragana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ア",
    "answer" : "a",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "イ",
    "answer" : "i",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ウ",
    "answer" : "u",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "エ",
    "answer" : "e",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "オ",
    "answer" : "o",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "カ",
    "answer" : "ka",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "キ",
    "answer" : "ki",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ク",
    "answer" : "ku",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ケ",
    "answer" : "ke",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "コ",
    "answer" : "ko",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "サ",
    "answer" : "sa",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "シ",
    "answer" : "shi",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ス",
    "answer" : "su",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "セ",
    "answer" : "se",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ソ",
    "answer" : "so",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "タ",
    "answer" : "ta",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "チ",
    "answer" : "chi",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ツ",
    "answer" : "tsu",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "テ",
    "answer" : "te",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ト",
    "answer" : "to",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ナ",
    "answer" : "na",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ニ",
    "answer" : "ni",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヌ",
    "answer" : "nu",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ネ",
    "answer" : "ne",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ノ",
    "answer" : "no",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ハ",
    "answer" : "ha",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヒ",
    "answer" : "hi",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "フ",
    "answer" : "fu",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヘ",
    "answer" : "he",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ホ",
    "answer" : "ho",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "マ",
    "answer" : "ma",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ミ",
    "answer" : "mi",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ム",
    "answer" : "mu",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "メ",
    "answer" : "me",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "モ",
    "answer" : "mo",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヤ",
    "answer" : "ya",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ユ",
    "answer" : "yu",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヨ",
    "answer" : "yo",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ラ",
    "answer" : "ra",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "リ",
    "answer" : "ri",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ル",
    "answer" : "ru",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "レ",
    "answer" : "re",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ロ",
    "answer" : "ro",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ワ",
    "answer" : "wa",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヲ",
    "answer" : "wo",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ン",
    "answer" : "n",
    "tagged" : [ "gojuon", "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ガ",
    "answer" : "ga",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ギ",
    "answer" : "gi",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "グ",
    "answer" : "gu",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ゲ",
    "answer" : "ge",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ゴ",
    "answer" : "go",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ザ",
    "answer" : "za",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ジ",
    "answer" : "ji",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ズ",
    "answer" : "zu",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ゼ",
    "answer" : "ze",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ゾ",
    "answer" : "zo",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ダ",
    "answer" : "da",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヂ",
    "answer" : "di",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ヅ",
    "answer" : "du",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "デ",
    "answer" : "de",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ド",
    "answer" : "do",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "バ",
    "answer" : "ba",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ビ",
    "answer" : "bi",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ブ",
    "answer" : "bu",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ベ",
    "answer" : "be",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ボ",
    "answer" : "bo",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "パ",
    "answer" : "pa",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ピ",
    "answer" : "pi",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "プ",
    "answer" : "pu",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ペ",
    "answer" : "pe",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ポ",
    "answer" : "po",
    "tagged" : [ "katakana" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "零|れい",
    "answer" : "zero",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "一|いち",
    "answer" : "one",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "ニ|に",
    "answer" : "two",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "三|さん",
    "answer" : "three",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "四|よん",
    "answer" : "four",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "五|ご",
    "answer" : "five",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "六|ろく",
    "answer" : "six",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "七|なな",
    "answer" : "seven",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "八|はち",
    "answer" : "eight",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "九|きゅう",
    "answer" : "nine",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "十|じゅう",
    "answer" : "ten",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "百|ひゃく",
    "answer" : "hundred",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "千|せん",
    "answer" : "thousand",
    "tagged" : [ "numbers" ]
  }]
}
